mysticalraven.com 2015-12-08

# Privacy Policy |

**Section 1 –  How do we use your information?**

Most websites will collect information from their visitors. Usually this will include IP addresses, browser type, and referring pages, things that Google Analytics or tracking codes would track. We use cookies to remember our visitors preferences and to help create a better experience for them when they are using our website. When we occasional do use advertisements, those cookies help us make sure that we are only creating relevant advertisements for our users. We do NOT sell any information to 3rd parties and we keep any data that we collect extremely confidential within our organization. Your email address will not be sold to third parties.

We allow third-party companies to serve  ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit:

**Section 2 – Consent**

If you provide us with any personal information, it is implied that you’re allowing us to collect it. If we are asking for information from you for a marketing purpose, we will directly ask for your consent and give you the opportunity to decline giving us that information.

**Section 3 – Our disclosure requirements**

If we are required by law to disclose your personal information, we do reserve that right.

**Section 4 – Links**

Any time you follow a link from our website to another, we aren’t responsible for the privacy policies of those other sites. We encourage you to read their private policies.

Additionally, we use Google Analytics to help us learn about you, the visitor! It doesn’t tell us too much, just what you’ve been checking out on the site.

**Section 5 – Third-party services**

Third-party groups will only be allowed the information voluntarily collected from you to allow them to provide a service to us (see: advertising). We will not sell your email address to third parties under any circumstance.

**Section 6 – Age of consent**

By using this website, you acknowledge that you are the age of consent in your state, province, or country, or that you are a consenting adult giving consent to a minor to use this website.

**Section 7 – Changes to this policy**

We reserve the ability to change this privacy policy at any time, so review it frequently. Changes take effect immediately upon posting on this website unless otherwise specified.

**Section 8 – Questions**

If you have any questions or comments please contact us [here](http://www.mysticalraven.com/about/contact-us/)

The following two tabs change content below.

  * Bio
  * Latest Posts

Raven Fon is a freelance writer and a globetrotting journalist. She studied creative writing and journalism at Saint Petersburg College and has since been a contributor to local newspapers, as well as several blogs including The Open Mind, Earth We Are One, and I Heart Intelligence.
